terasgames.com 2016-11-03

# Teras Games - All the Best Games, Always Free

## Privacy Policy

### Introduction

This Privacy Policy applies to all users of the Teras Games Apps and the Site. This Privacy Policy describes the Company's collection and use of users' personal information and non-personally identifiable information. Teras Games Apps should only be installed by users that are of the age of 18 or older. Users under the age of 18 should ask for parental/guardian approval.

### Collection of Information

#### User Submitted Information

Users are not required to create an account or register to use Teras Games Apps. However, when contacting us for issues related to the Teras Games Apps, you may submit personal information to allow us to effectively respond to your inquiry or request.

#### Collected Information

When users access or use the Teras Games Apps, certain non-personally identifiable information is collected, stored and used for business and marketing purposes. This non-personally identifiable information includes, without limitation: IP address, unique identifier number, operating system, browser and other software information, webpage URLs visited, and search queries entered. This collected data may also be supplemented with information obtained from third parties.

We use cookies to collect aggregate Internet traffic statistics and to better understand our users, which allow us to enhance your experience at the Site. This data may include storing user preferences and product utilization information such as number of visitors, average time spent on pages, features used, and other information which help us determine which features are most important to you and working effectively. If you do not want the Site to deploy cookies in your browser, you can set your browser to reject cookies or to notify you when a website tries to put a cookie in your browser software. If you choose to decline cookies, however, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Site and it may affect your ability to use some of the services at the Site. We do not tie any PII to the cookies that we set.

Third parties that support Teras Games Apps by serving advertisements may also use cookies and other tracking technologies described above to collect similar information. The Company does not control these third parties and their use of these technologies is governed by the privacy policies of the third parties using such technologies.

### Use & Disclosure of Information

Information collected from and about users may be used for the following purposes:

We use the information collected to deliver the Teras Games Apps to you, to measure and improve the Teras Games Apps, to personalize your experience by delivering applicable content and advertising, and to provide you with customer support. We may use aggregated or anonymous data about use of and activity on the Teras Games Apps to assist us in this regard and such data is not subject to this Privacy Policy.

To allow third party service providers to assist us in providing and managing the Teras Games Apps. The Company may make your non-public personal information available to certain third party service providers, such as contractors or agents, who help us manage or provide the Teras Games Apps. Such examples of Teras Games Apps include, without limitation: advertising and marketing, developing or supporting products and functionalities, and processing data or statistics. These outside service providers are required to protect non-public personal information entrusted to them and not use it for any other purpose than the specific service they are providing to the Company.

We may use the information you provide to us, and information we collect about your use of the Teras Games Apps through cookies and other technologies, to assist us in delivering you relevant ads when you use the Teras Games Apps. We may work with third party advertising networks and advertisers who help deliver these ads to you. We may share anonymous, non- personally identifiable or aggregated information with third parties to improve the relevancy of the ads you see using the Teras Games Apps. As noted above, these third party advertising networks and advertisers may also use cookies and similar technologies to collect and track non-personally identifiable information such as demographic information, aggregated information, and Internet activity to assist them in delivering advertising that is more relevant to your interests.

There may be instances when the Company may disclose user information without providing notice or choice, including situations where the Company has a good faith belief that such disclosure is necessary in order to: (i) protect or defend the legal rights or property of the Company, our affiliated companies or their employees, agents and contractors (ii) protect the safety and security of users of the Teras Games Apps; (iii) protect against fraud or for risk management purposes; or (iv) comply with the law or legal process.

### Security

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personally identifiable information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

### Children's Privacy

We do not knowingly collect personal data from children or collect data from anyone under the age of 13.

### User Control and Uninstalling Software

Chrome uninstall instructions: 

  1. Go to Settings within Chrome browser
  2. Click on Extensions
  3. Uncheck the Enabled box or click Trash icon to delete the extension 
  4. Close and restart your browser

Firefox uninstall instructions: 

  1. Click the button with three horizontal lines located at the top right of your browser
  2. Click Add-ons 
  3. Select the Extensions tab from the navigation options listed on the left
  4. Find the extension you are looking to remove and click the Remove button
  5. Close and restart your browser

Internet Explorer uninstall instructions 

  1. Click the Settings wheel icon located at the top right of your browser
  2. Click Manage add-ons
  3. Select the Search Providers from the navigation options listed on the left
  4. You will need to choose another search provider to “Set as Default”
  5. Once another search provider is set as default you can select the other search option and click Remove
  6. Close and restart your browser

To change your Internet Explorer home page, please follow these instructions: 

  1. Click the Settings wheel icon located at the top right of your browser
  2. Click Internet options
  3. Change the home page destination to your preferred home page and click Apply to save your changes
  4. Click Ok to close the window
  5. Close and restart your browser

For more detailed uninstall instructions, please visit our uninstall page. 

### Questions and Concerns

If you have any questions or concerns about the Privacy Policy or its implementation, please email us at [support@terasgames.com](mailto:support@terasgames.com).
